These
are the
most
common
questions
our
customers
ask
us.
Does
the vehicle
start
and
is it
ready
to
drive?
Not all
the
vehicles
start
and
are
ready
to
drive.
That's why
we do
everything
possible
to
send
photos and
videos
so you
know
their
condition
before
buying.
What's
the lowest
you'll go?
Our
salespeople
will always
do
everything
possible
to
offer you
the best
price
and reach
a
deal
that's fair
for
both
parties.
Do you
ship?
We ship
anywhere
in
the
United
States and
to other
countries.
We also
help
you
get
the
best
price
on
transport.
Do you
give
repair
estimates?
We can
give you
some
guidance
based
on
our
experience
and the
information
available.
But a
final
estimate
always
comes from
a shop
after
they
inspect
the
vehicle.
Does this
work
like an
auction?
No.
We're a
dealer
specializing
in wrecked
cars
for
repair.
You can
come
inspect them
yourself
or see
what we
have in
stock on
our
website,
ayofmayami.com.
And if
you have
another
question,
don't hesitate
to
write us.